Hello friends, welcome to Stock Movers.
Friends, you are new to our channel. Please
subscribe to our channel and press the bell
icon. Friends,
why are we asking you to leave HDFC Live?
Friends, first of all I want to tell you
that today we can
talk about ICC Prudential. This stock
saw a rise of about 10%, which
is intraday. Friends, after that there is
some decline, but
friends I want to tell you that till the last moment
this stock sees a rise,
friends. But yes, you know friends, there is some
profit booking
in such a market. So the second important
part, friends, if we talk about HDFC, then
you can do flat trading, which is
flat trading. But in such a situation,
ICC Prudential friends, I want to tell you
that today it showed a rise of 9 to 10%.
In the last phase, still,
7% to 6% was seen, but friends, I
want to tell you that there are already many twists
in this stock, related to which
we will talk and whether this stock should be booked
or not, friends.
Related to which we can talk about ICC
Prudential, as you can see, if you
talk about the company, then today
you will see friends that this company has
shown a rise of around 7%, friends, what does it
mean to say rise, that here this
stock opens on the previous date,
friends, after that there is a
good rise here, then a slight
fall, then friends, if you see,
you can see this rise only till the last bar, but
yes, friends, some
profit booking has been seen here, if we
talk about the company, then
why was there so much rise in this stock, first of all friends, I
want to tell that Anup Bachchi
friends, HD and Co have been
appointed in the company, however,
friends, where did he come from, then it should be told
friends, he was within the company,
friends, he was working in ICC Bank earlier,
as you can see here also,
since 1992, or that means in this group,
friends, he has been working since 1992, meaning
friends, after his arrival, it is possible that the
stock may have a change.  If we talk about a good stock or
company, then strength can be seen,
where is it present, friends, I
want to tell you that this is the
Executive Director of ICC Bank,
who was present and he was also working as a non-
executive director,
as soon as friends this news has come, now you
can see how much the company has put on HI,
friends ₹460 means ₹415, the company has put on HI around ₹20, if you
see, it recovers up to 10%,
if we
talk about the company, then how much the company has
put on HI, friends, today the
company also put a HI of 380,
then friends, after the performance, the
stock failed 26% against 2% decline in the
benchmark index, friends, yes you
can talk about the company, for how many days was he
appointed, friends, he has been
appointed for 5 years, from June
19, 2023, that is, he will
handle the work, friends, regulatory  Approval will be given
friends, after that see who is the
director of the executive director,
friends who is the garden here from 2023 onwards,
friends the subject to regulatory approval will be
seen friends, if seen then it will be
affected on June 18, 2022,
friends who were there earlier, friends who are SN Kannan, that
means he will retire now, that means friends he will
retire,
friends say retirement, you can do this
if the company appointment on June 18, 2023
is during Trainer S ICC
Prudential, that means
you will not get to see the successful news sir, in such a situation,
however friends I want to tell you that a lot of
details are already there in this company,
if you look at its 5 year chart, then
in 5 years the company has
not given any return, if you look at the chart of this stock, then the
chart of this stock will also show you very
high volatile, if
I talk about the chart pattern, then
since the company came, it has given a return of only 32%,
talk about this company 310
This company gets listed in the market on September 30, 2016, at a price of Rs.
Friends,
after that this company also shows something special
that is not its performance. If you
talk about HDFC Life, then if you look at HDFC Live, then a
decline of about one percent has been
seen in this stock as well.
Friends, now if you look at the previous close, then friends, from the
previous closing,
friends, it opens down and
after that, some recovery takes place.
Friends, a decline is seen in this stock as well.
In this too, the process is like this Nifty
stock, in such a situation, life insurance keeps
coming, what does the company do,
friends, so this company is also a small
company, friends, this is also an ICC group
company, friends, this also does life insurance, we can
talk about the company. Today, the
total seat tradeway in this stock is around 10 million, which is the
value achieved today. Friends, I want to tell you
that this stock trades in lakhs,
as you can see, yes, if we
talk about the delivery percentage, then nothing
special, but friends, I want to tell you that this
company was also registering a decline from many times, as
Even today the company has
appointed a new person, you can see it here too
friends, meaning
you will see less of it in the green mark and a lot more in the red mark.
Talking about the delivery percentage, it is around 50-60%,
friends I
want to tell you that there is something special in it that the
goods were not being lifted.
Talking about before this, the goods were lifted only above 50%, so
talking about NCL friends, as
you can see, today itself you will see the
arrow here in the red mark.
Talking about the company, it seems that the high of 2 September
2012 is seen. On
March 2030, the company's low is Rs 380, which is
today's. If we talk about balloon, there is
a good volume created in this stock, you
know, around 8-9 million 10
million total seats were traded in
which, if you have seen, then the delivery percentage, the
goods were not lifted that much, meaning
friends, this is also a negative point.
In the matter of appreciation, friends, we don't need a lot of
details.  I don't need to know, it's
time to talk about the company, this is a company that does life
insurance business, friends, let's
talk about the company,
you can be the promoter of this company of ICC Bank, which is the
second largest private bank, which owns
50%, 51% of the stock, and
look here, friends, Prudential
Life Insurance, friends, which owns 22%, which you can
see, this is a
foreign company,
this company has business in London at the global level,
but friends, this is also a big cap company,
market cap of 58000 crore, 60 thousand crore,
current price is 4009, we have seen every side,
low side, then if we look at the point of P, then it is
hi,
friends, I want to tell you that this is a
company of the insurance sector, friends, it is in
loss, being in loss means,
friends, I want to tell you that the insurance
sector is such a sector that there is a
little uncertain environment here too, so
friends, talking about the book value, it is 17, sorry,
70, the company pays some dividend
and if we look at this, then so much  The
face value of 10 is not special. Talking about this company, if we have
seen it in the sector, then the company has come at number four
after HDFC Life, friends,
this company has also come at number four, see, this is also
a small company, yes,
in terms of valuation, friends, I told you that you
can see that this is at the highest, you
can talk about the quarterly rate of the company, such
companies which do sales, friends, you will
see the sales, there is a
jump in all of them, but friends,
if you look at the real profit, then the company
which is in the mines, friends,
their profit, which
comes from income, then you will also see the ideal income,
friends, so the company's air and this is only the
DR in quarters, that is,
friends, you will also see the charts in the same way,
almost the company is
going on, if we talk about net profit, then we
can see it, there is a DR on the channel, if
we
look at the panel of the company, the DR is visible in the TTM itself
and in 2022 also, friends, now we
can see that the same DR will be seen,
in 2021 they did good sales.
If we talk about operating profit, then if we have
seen the operating profit till now, then the
company is in loss. If we
talk about the other income of the company continuously for 4 years, then other income has
also been seen, then the company has grown. If we
talk about the net profit of the company, if we have
seen the net profit, then
you can say that the company is in growing mode. If we
talk about the sales growth of the company, then if we look at the sales growth of the company, then it
is negative in TTM, but
yes, if we talk about profit growth of around 10 to 15%, then the
profit of the company
is negative. As friends, we
told you that many life insurance
companies, friends, remain in loss, so if we
talk about such friends, then it is
seen to be negative.
If we talk about the balance sheet of the company, then if you
can talk about the debt of the company in terms of eight to nine thousand crores, then there is a
debt of 1200 crores. As friends, we
told you that there are only two promoters in it,
so friends, the biggest
majority state which has to be kept on and
if we talk about the second, friends  Providential
Corporation Holdings Limited, which I
saw is a global business,
friends, this company also has a
22% stock, if I were to talk about it, the
prices are selling in this stock, I
mean, this quarter
they have closed, the
biggest positive sign, friends, I
want to tell you that the stock in this stock is being sold, that is,
friends, the
biggest trust here,
ICC Bank, friends, this is also
not a small group, friends, this company
also has as much business as HDFC Bank,
if we talk about the public, then the
public has also been selling,
friends, what should we do now, first of all, I
want to tell you that the
investors who are buying the bank after seeing this rise, from
my point of view, if you want, you
can avoid this stock by watching the button right now, because friends, I want to tell you
that this company also belongs to the life
insurance sector, so
friends, how are the companies in the life insurance sector performing at this time,
you know, friends, tell me about that too.  I
want to know that the fourth number company has come, which is the
biggest giant company, friends, you have also
seen the link, so it is struggling a lot at this time due to
valuation, if we
talk about the company, friends, then the growth that this company has
shown today, friends, it has shown growth
related to the management, it has shown growth
related to the appointment, so
friends, if you want, you can wait and watch for a day or two,
or see how this stock will
react on Monday, what will happen tomorrow,
friends, you can probably do a little bit of baton watching,
keep an eye on it, yes,
second, if we talk, this stock has a
lot of desktop fans, so I
want to tell you this much, friends, if you want, you can
hold this stock and go for the long term, you can talk about the stock, the
stock is good, there is nothing wrong,
friends, yes, right now it is a little bit that
this stock is struggling, friends,
in the coming future, friends, all these stocks can give
themselves good returns, the
market is also expecting this
and also friends, you have seen that the
goods are going up for a minute,
friends  And this is also a trusted company,
so you can hold for the long term.
Second, if we were to talk about those who are considering banking on the stock, if
you want to bank on the current price, then
this stock could fall and reach
350. If we talk about the higher side, then
this stop, if the current time is
positive, friends, friends, friends, see, the
management has a lot of
experience and in the G sector,
friends, they are working in retail corporate,
friends, I have seen in that, so
far they have shown only growth,
so friends, for this,
this stock has seen a rise in the market today, so it is
possible that
in the coming future, if we talk about some life insurance, that is, the
life insurance
company's business, then it is possible that it has the
potential to see some growth, so
in such a situation, whoever you want, you can
hold for the long term, if you can
fall to 300, if we talk about the side, it can
also trade above 500.
Thank you friends.